Finding Aid for Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated
Clarke Historical Library
- Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated.
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #470 Rev. Al Sharpton,undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #471 Spring Lake, Fochtman Sign Round Lake (bad) T. Bailey 2,undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #472 Bay View/ River 31 N and S, Glens, Farms Wal-Mart,undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #473 FaCIT (Faculty Center for Innovative Technology) Promo B-Roll,undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #475 FBI Whistleblower Coleen Rowley Ethics Class,undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #476 Human Olympics,undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #477 Exhibits Steve [Smith],undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #478 Zeigler News Conference,undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #479 Tsunami Relief,undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #480 Dow Mock Drill,undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #481 Duct Tape Dude,undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #482 Korean Volleyball,undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacanSP #483 Tom Borrelli,undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #484 Waken huts,undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #485 SAC IM (intramural) Rugby,undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #486 Adopt a Grandpa,undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #487 Listserve.edu Cyber Feast,undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #488 Speech clinic,undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Videotapes Masters: Betacan #489 Indian Dancers Tape #2,undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #490 Sports Facility,undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #491 Get Acquainted Day, Fire Up Fest,2005 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #492 Wet Lab Groundbreaking,2005 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #493 Robert Boy,undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #494 Polar Tech,undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #495 Gagnon Mp of y,undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #496 Coach Carter,undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #655 Alumni Golf Outing, Interview for Margo Jonker,undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #656 AAIA (Association on American Indian Affairs), Native American Family Olympics,2007 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #657 Margo Jonker Youth Softball Camp,2007 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #658 Margo Jonker, Julie Maxon, Leslie (Grimes) Phelan (Part 1),2007 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #659 Margo Jonker, Julie Maxon, Leslie (Grimes) Phelan (Part 2),2007 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #660 Butch Jones Welcome For Scoreboard,2007 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #661 USA Softball highlights, Margo Jonker,undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #662 Margo Jonker News Conference,2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #663 Christina Vecchioni, Standups for State Champs, Tape #2,2007 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #664 Christina Vecchioni, Standups for State Champs, Tape #1,2007 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #665 Dave Heeke Interview for Margo Jonker Video and Scoreboard,2007 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #666 Amy Vandermerine Interview for Margo Jonker Video,2007 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #667 Marcy Weston Interview for Margo Jonker Video, Tape #2,2007 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #668 Marcy Weston Interview for Margo Jonker Video, Tape #1,2007 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #669 CMU Spots Tape 1, Dave G. Broll Interview,2007 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #670 CMU Spots Tape 1, Gill and Luis Interviews,2007 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #671 CMU Spots Tape 1, Jim Felton Interview, B-Roll,2007 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #672 CMU Spots Tape 1, Jim Felton Interview,2007 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #673 CMU B-Roll for Fall 2007 Image Spots, Printed to Tape from Quicktime Files, Not Camera Originals,2007 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #675 Gail Torreano Interview, B-Roll, Tape #2,2007 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #676 Gail Torreano Interview, B-Roll, Tape #1,2007 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #677 This is Central, Laura Interview, B-Roll, Tape #1,2007 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #678 This is Central, Laura Interview, Camie, B-Roll, Tape #2,2007undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Videotapes Masters:BetacamSP #679 This is Central, Laura Interview, Camie, B-Roll, Tape #12007 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #680 This is Central, Steve Interview, Tape #4,2007 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #681 R. Barclay Photo Exhibit, B-Roll,2007 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #682 United Way Campaign Kickoff at Central Park,2007 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #683 Kevin Corbett Interview for MSF Inside Central,2007 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #684 Fire Up Fest,2007 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #685 Michigan Story Festival Narration Steve Smith,2006 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #686 Admissions Interviews Tape #1,undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #687 Admissions Interviews Tape #2,undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #688 Admissions Interviews Tape #3,undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #689 Admissions Interviews Tape #4,undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #690 Admissions Interviews Tape #5,undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #575 Butch Jones Press Conference Tape #1,2007 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #576 Butch Jones Press Conference Tape #2,2007 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #577 Jessica Wojciechowski Stand Up for State Champs,2007 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #578 MLK (Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.) Unity March,2007 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #579 Jesse Jackson Press Conference,2007 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #580 Jesse Jackson Speech Tape #1,2007 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #581 Jesse Jackson Speech Tape #2,2007 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #582 Jesse Jackson Interview,2007 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #583 Jesse Jackson Q and A (Questions and Answers),2007 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #584 Trisha Laglois Interview on Residence Halls, Celani and Towers, B-Roll,2007 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP BetacamSP #585 Jessica Wojciechowski Stand Up, Residence Halls and Leadership (State Champs), Res Hall Fitness Center B-Roll,2007 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #586 Res Hall B-Roll, Rooms, Restaurant, Club Room, Market Comp Lab, Celani/ Fabiano Complex,2007 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #587 Leadership Classroom R-Roll and Jessica Wojciechowski Stand Up (State Champs!),2007 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #588 Dan Church Interview and Leadership Classroom (State Champs),2007 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #589 Jessica Wojciechowski Stand Up, State Champs!,2007 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #590 Wayne Osborn, Inside Central, Research Prominence,2007 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #591 President Mike Rao Interview, Inside Central, Research Ranking Segment,2007 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #592 Career Services B-Roll,2007 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #593 Heather Smith Stand-Up For IC, Culture Crawl, Classroom, B-Roll,2007 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #594 Heather Hillman State Champs! Tape #2,2007 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #595 Heather Hillman State Champs! Tape #1,2007 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #596 State Champs! Laura Cochran Amanda Hagy Interviews,2007 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #597 State Champs! Amanda Hagy, Felisha Arvdary (no Good), Mike Foss Interviews,2007 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #598 Dani Hiar – Lab Rescue for Inside Central,2007 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #599 Dani Hiar –Lab Rescue B-Roll, Dogs Playing in Backyard,2007 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #600 Touchdowns,undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #601 Jessica Wojciechowski Stand Ups for State Champs, Tape #1,2007 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #602 Jessica Wojciechowski Stand Ups for State Champs, Tape #2, Library and Art Fredericks, B-Roll,2007 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #603 Art Fredericks Interview for Inside Central,2007 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #604 Keith Helferich Interview for Inside Central, Logistics Professor,2007 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #605 Keith Helferich Interview for Inside Central, B-Roll, Short,2007 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #606 State Champs – SAC (Student Activity Center) Interviews,2007 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #607 Jessica Wojciechowski Mentor Minute Stand Ups,2007 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #608 Alexandra Mascolo-David Interview for IC 605,2007 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #609 CMU Driving Stimulator VNR,2007 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #610 Faculty Excellence Awards Tape #1,2007 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #611 Faculty Excellence Awards Tape #2,2007 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #612 Math, Sci, Tech Trimester #2,undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #613 Amy Roloff Classroom Talk ConCAA Neely-Prof,2007 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #614 Amy Roloff Dinner and Speech Tape #1,2007 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #41 Masonic Home Health Interview Michael Dodman Speech Languages, Pathology, Interview Coughlin in Class,undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #42 ED Funding Bill,Spring 2000 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #43 Charter School Institute Open House, Tape #1, Student Exhibit, Engler Touring Building,2000 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #44 Charter School Institute Open House, Tape #2, Speeches, Ribbon Cutting, Building Exterior,2000 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #45 Triplets in Barnes,undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Videotapes Masters: #46 Pres. Rao Appointment and Press Conference,2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #47 Intelligence Test, Tape #1, Interviews w Sharon and Carl Johnson, Johnson’s Intelligence Test given to baby,undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #48 Intelligence Test given to 3-yr-old, Tape #2,undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #50 NAISO Meeting, Get Acquainted Day,1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #51 Special Olympics Polar Plunge Belleville, MI,2001 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #52 Campus Scenics,Spring 1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #53 no label may be Speech Therapy/Masonic Home Interview Coughlin Class CHP,undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #54 CMU License Plate,undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #55 Plachta at Society of State Dedication,undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #56 no label (may be Speech Therapy/Masonic Home Interview Coughlin Class CHP),undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #57 Freshman Empowerment Tape #2,undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #58 Shingles Interview, Football Taping,undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #59 Ethanol Research, 1998; Asian Heritage/ Lion Dance, 1999,1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #60 Colin Powell, Detroit, Colin Powell Academy,1997 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #61 Battle of the Bands,2000 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #62 Martin Reinhardt, CMU Minute, graphic design,1997 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #63 Diversity Forum, CMU Minute Student Success,undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #64 Various Business Classes, Accreditation Logo, LaBelle Entrepreneurial Center Sign,undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #65 Kosovo Prisoners Press Conference, Plachta Testimonials,undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #66 Leadership Camp,1998 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #67 Interactive Classroom CEL,undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #68 no label,undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #69 no label,undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #70 Student Research Expo,2000 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #71 CEEP (College Education Enhancement Program for minorities) Class, John Dinse, Hispanic Taster, Mariachi Band,undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #72 KCP (King/ Chavez/ Parks) Program,2000 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #73 MLK March, Black History Display- Multicultural Center, Soul Food Taster, #1003,1997 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #74 Kwanza Dancers, Gospel Singers, #1000, African American Events,undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #75 International Expo,1995 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #76 CMU and You Day, Football Team March to Stadium,2000 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #77 CEL (College of Extended Learning) Computer Lab, IET (Industrial Engineering and Technology) Robot Lab,undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #78 Sports Website, Students Return to Campus,2000 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #79 Towers Computer Lab,undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #80 GIS, Resident Hall, B-Roll,1998 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #81 IET/ Habitat House, Troy CEL Class,1997 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #497: MLK Interview B-Roll,undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #498 Family Olympics Tape #1,undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #499 Family Olympics Tape #2,undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #500 Dan Mastramaonaco,undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #501 Pat Cocharan, Real Estate,undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #502 Larry King - Big Brothers and Big Sisters, Glenn and Angela Stanton,undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #503 JoAnn Hinds, Beaver Island, New Vision of Excellence,undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #504 Scholarship Donors,undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #505 Scholarship Donors Tape #2,undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #506 Audiology Class and One On One,undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #507 CMU Promise Tape #1,undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #508 CMU Promise Tape #2,undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #509 Dave Keilitz,undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #510 Herb Deromedi,undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #511 Herb Deromedi Stuff,undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #512 Marcy Weston,undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #513 CEL SOT’s #2,undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #514 Herb Deromedi Stuff,undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #515 Polartech Presentations,undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #516 Sports Apparel Presentatins to Rebok,2006? (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #517 Football Stadium Light Installation,undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #518 Clare Playscape RPLS Student Volunteers and Faculty,2006 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #519 Honors Interview Jim Hill,undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #520 Honors Interview Lindsey Wahowiak, Laura Bantle,undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #521 Honors Interview Mahlon Collins (Pickford Sr. Honors Alum), Stephen June,undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #522 Honors Interview Jenna Rickman, Emily Doerr,undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #523 Honors Interview Emily Doerr, Dan Nowiski,undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #524 Honors Interview Jessica Wojeiechowski, Dan Nowiski,undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #525 Honors Interview Jenna Rickman, Philip Voss,undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #526 Interviews for SagChip Brian Kelly, Ronnie Ekdahl,undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #527 Capital Campaign Gala, Tape #1,2006 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #528 Capital Campaign Gala, Tape #2,2006 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #529 SagChip Pres. Rao and Chief Canto,2006 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #530 SagChip PSA, CMU Public Relations and Marketing, Tape #2,2006 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #531 Driving Simulator Tape #1, Dr. Rick Backs,2006 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #532 Driving Simulator Tape #2, Dr. Rick Backs,2006 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #534 WMHW Alumni Takeover, BCA, Tape #1,2006 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #535 Campus B-Roll, Warriner Mall, Park Library sidewalk, Anspach, Pearce, Dow Mall,2006 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Videotapes Masters: BetacamSP #536 Terri Lynn Carrington Tape #1,undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #1 Broadway Theater,undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #2 Gear Up,undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #3 Gear Up workshop,undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #4 Op for Talent Development #1,Summer 2000 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP BetacamSP #5 Op for Talent Development #2,Summer 2000 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #6 Gerald Ford Program #1, 30 minutes,undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #7 Gerald Ford Program #2, 16:44,undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #8 DB Central,undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #9 Homecoming Parade,2000 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #10 Renee Shingles on TV Sports Medicine B-Roll,undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #11 no label,undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #12 Gait Research, Residential College, 1999; Dorm Dining and Lounge, UC #1,1999s (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #13 no label,undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #14 no label,undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #15 Water Research Center,undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #16 Sturgeon Research #1,undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #17 Sturgeon Research #2,undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #18 Sturgeon Research #3,undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #19 Beaver Island Tape #1,undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #20 Beaver Island Tape #2,undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #21 Beaver Island Tape #3,undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #22 Beaver Island Tape #4, John News Interview, Deer, Monarch Larvae and butterfly, Miller’s Marsh, Lori Kindsvatter Snake Research, Jim Gillingham, Interview,1998 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #23 Beaver Island Tape #5,undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #24 Health Expo,undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #25 Steve Kapp Interview, Physician Assistant B-Roll,1998 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #26 Perch Research,1998 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP 27 Hippotherapy,undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #28 Human Fitness Lab,undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #29 Healthy Hearts Program,undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #30 Sports Medicine (editorial note: Old facilities so use closeups),undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #31 Physical Therapy,1997 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #32 No label,undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #33Prek Class Pa at MD’s Office,undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #34 Operation B-Roll,undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #35 no label,undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Videotapes, #1-40:: BetacamSP #36 Audiology Clinic, PA in MD’s Office,undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - VVideotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #37 Audiology, Homecoming Parade,1998 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #38 Audiology Clinic B-Roll,undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #39 Interviews Wellness Central,undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Videotapes, #1-40: BetacamSP #40 no label,undated (Box 12, Folder 40)